(AIR QUAVERING)
(UPBEAT HIP-HOP MUSIC)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(SHOES CLACKING)
- YO, WHAT'S UP?
- YO, WHERE WE AT, MAN?
- WHERE BABY DOLL COME FROM?
- WHO PUT THIS FUNNY
LOOKIN' SHIRT ON ME, YO?
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN,
BUT I'M GONNA GO
CHECK Y'ALL OUT MAN.
- WHERE'S LIONEL AT, MAN?
I GOTTA, I GOTTA TALK
TO HIM ABOUT SOMETHIN'.
- OH, YEAH, BACK TO THE VIDEO.
♪ POISON ♪
♪ YEAH, SPYDERMAN AND
FREEZE IN FULL EFFECT ♪
♪ UH-HUH ♪
♪ YOU READY, RON ♪
♪ I'M READY ♪
♪ YOU READY, BIV ♪
♪ I'M READY, SLICK, ARE YOU ♪
♪ OH, YEAH, BREAK IT DOWN ♪
♪ GIRL, I, MUST WARN YOU ♪
♪ I SENSE SOMETHING
STRANGE IN MY MIND ♪
♪ YEAH, YO ♪
♪ SITUATION IS SERIOUS ♪
♪ LET'S CURE IT CAUSE
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME ♪
♪ TELL 'EM RICK ♪
♪ IT'S OH, SO BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ RELATIONSHIPS THEY
SEEM FROM THE START ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ IT'S ALL SO DEADLY ♪
♪ WHEN LOVE IS NOT
TOGETHER FROM THE HEART ♪
♪ CHECK IT OUT ♪
♪ IT'S DRIVIN' ME
OUT OF MY MIND ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY IT'S
HARD FOR ME TO FIND ♪
♪ CAN'T GET IT OUT OF MY HEAD ♪
♪ MISS HER, KISS HER, LOVE HER ♪
♪ WRONG MOVE, YOU'RE DEAD ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS POISON ♪
♪ NEVER TRUST A BIG
BUTT AND A SMILE ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS POISON ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ IF I WERE YOU I'D
TAKE PRE-CAUTION ♪
♪ BEFORE I START TO MEET
A FLY GIRL, YOU KNOW ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IN SOME PORTIONS ♪
♪ YOU'LL THINK SHE'S THE
BEST THING IN THE WORLD ♪
♪ SHE'S SO FLY ♪
♪ SHE'LL DRIVE YOU
RIGHT OUT OF YOUR MIND ♪
♪ AND STEAL YOUR HEART
WHEN YOU'RE BLIND ♪
♪ BEWARE SHE'S SCHEMIN' ♪
♪ SHE'LL MAKE YOU
THINK YOU'RE DREAMIN' ♪
♪ YOU'LL FALL IN LOVE AND YOU'LL
BE SCREAMING, DEMON, OOH ♪
♪ POISON, DEADLY,
MOVIN' IN SLOW ♪
♪ LOOKIN' FOR A MELLOW
FELLOW LIKE DEVOE ♪
♪ GETTIN' PAID, LAID,
SO BETTER LAY LOW ♪
♪ SCHEMIN' ON HOUSE,
MONEY, AND THE WHOLE SHOW ♪
♪ THE LOW PRO, SHE'LL
BE CUT LIKE AN AFRO ♪
♪ SO, WHAT YOU'RE SAYIN',
HUH, SHE'S A WINNER TO YOU ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW SHE'S A LOSER ♪
♪ HOW DO YOU KNOW ♪
♪ ME AND THE CREW
USED TO DO HER ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ POISON, POISON,
POISON, POISON ♪
♪ I WAS AT THE BAR, SHAKE,
BREAKIN' AND TAKIN 'EM ALL ♪
♪ AND THAT NIGHT,
I PLAYED THE WALL ♪
♪ CHECKIN' OUT THE FELLAS,
THE HIGHS AND LOWS ♪
♪ KEEPIN' ONE EYE OPEN,
STILL CLOCKIN' THE ♪
♪ THERE WAS ONE PARTICULAR GIRL
THAT STOOD OUT FROM THE REST ♪
♪ POISON AS CAN BE,
THE HIGH POWER CHEST ♪
♪ MICHAEL BIVINS HERE AND
I'M RUNNIN' THE SHOW ♪
♪ BELL BIV DEVOE (LAUGHING) ♪
♪ NOW YOU KNOW ♪
♪ YO, SLICK, BLOW ♪
♪ IT'S DRIVIN' ME
OUT OF MY MIND ♪
♪ THAT'S WHY IT'S
HARD FOR ME TO FIND ♪
♪ CAN'T GET IT OUT OF MY HEAD ♪
♪ MISS HER, KISS HER, LOVE HER ♪
♪ WRONG MOVE, YOU'RE DEAD ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS POISON, HOO ♪
♪ POISON, HOO ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ NEVER TRUST A BIG
BUTT AND A SMILE ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ SHE'S DANGEROUS ♪
♪ POISON, OH, YEAH ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ YO, FELLAS, THAT
WAS MY END OF ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYIN', MIKE ♪
♪ YEAH, BBD IN FULL EFFECT ♪
♪ YO, WASSUP TO RALPH
T AND JOHNNY G ♪
♪ YEAH, AND I CAN'T FORGET
ABOUT MY BOY, B. BROWN ♪
♪ AND THE WHOLE NE CREW ♪
♪ POISON ♪
♪ A-HA ♪
(MEMBERS LAUGHING)